{
    "id": "ea01e57ca38a4d1086b04fdf460e6763",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .................................... the bell twice.",
            "description": "Rang is the simple past of ring.",
            "answers": [
                "rang",
                "ringed",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d995af14e604080a78bc594f6ced413"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ....................................... the violin?",
            "description": "Brought is the simple past of bring.",
            "answers": [
                "bringed",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed136ff871e841f8b369b1fcbd69bda6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat has ....................................... the milk.",
            "description": "Drunk is the past participle form of drink.",
            "answers": [
                "drank",
                "drinked",
                "drunk"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb35d4f8d7df45dfa582a0b754068625"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ..................................... the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "done",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c9959ff2f1047068508a47ffbe89ab1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ...................................... a well in the backyard.",
            "description": "Dug is the past simple and past participle of dig. ",
            "answers": [
                "dig",
                "digged",
                "dug"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "61530570e85940f9a9411395543a8701"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................................... the clothes out.",
            "description": "The past simple of wring is wrang or wrung. ",
            "answers": [
                "wringed",
                "wrang",
                "wrung"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6065726681674a348caee82a3cf7e6b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ..................................... a lot on his children's education.",
            "description": "Spent is the past simple and past participle form of spend.",
            "answers": [
                "spent",
                "spend",
                "spended"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9bd5e975a70f4fc688669f44caf1f9f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How you have ....................................!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "grew",
                "growed",
                "grown"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "88b0fa29ca9043b3b8f68a7ced8613b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ........................................ to Australia.",
            "description": "We use been for finished visit. If somebody has gone to Australia, they are still in Australia. ",
            "answers": [
                "gone",
                "been",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "78f59e9b723242a2914b5a549f6a7864"
        },
        {
            "question": "The place ........................................ like a sewer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stink",
                "stinked",
                "stank"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b13d9df4142c45809d72227bc2f66f28"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter ......................................... under his breath.",
            "description": "Sweared is possible in a careless style. ",
            "answers": [
                "sweared",
                "swore",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07b293b63e434aa58cf9efd6885ded7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ......................................... the grains into powder.",
            "description": "Ground is the past simple of grind. ",
            "answers": [
                "grinded",
                "grounded",
                "ground"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bccea6ffc56743d1a2513eeab5c7af5c"
        }
    ]
}